[
  {
    "question": "Which network security tool can you use to control traffic in and out of EC2 Instances?",
    "options": [
      "Network Access Control Lists (NACL)",
      "Identity and Management Access (IAM)",
      "GuardDuty",
      "Security Groups"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Under the Shared Responsibility Model, who is responsible for operating-system patches and updates on EC2 Instances?",
    "options": [
      "The Customer",
      "AWS",
      "Both AWS and the Customer",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A company would like to deploy a high-performance computing (HPC) application on EC2. Which EC2 instance type should it choose?",
    "options": [
      "Storage Optimized",
      "Compute Optimized",
      "Memory Optimized",
      "General Purpose"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "EC2 is a Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS is responsible for configuring Security Groups rules?",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis.",
      "Customers retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances.",
      "Customers can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads.",
      "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on-demand when needed."
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "If your project requires monthly reports that iterate through very large amounts of data, which Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) purchasing option should you consider?",
    "options": [
      "Spot Instances",
      "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
      "Dedicated Hosts",
      "On-Demand Instances"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is included in an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?",
    "options": [
      "A template for the root volume for the instance",
      "Launch permissions that control which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch instances.",
      "A block device mapping that specifies the volumes to attach to the instance when it's launched",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) feature ensures your instances will not share a physical host with instances from any other AWS customer?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon VPC",
      "Placement groups",
      "Dedicated Instances",
      "Reserved Instances"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Your web application needs four instances to support steady traffic all of the time. On the last day of the month, the traffic triples. What is the most cost-effective way to handle this pattern?",
    "options": [
      "Run 12 Reserved Instances all of the time.",
      "Run four On-Demand Instances constantly, then add eight more On-Demand Instances on the last day of each month.",
      "Run four Reserved Instances constantly, then add eight On-Demand Instances on the last day of each month.",
      "Run four On-Demand Instances constantly, then add eight Reserved Instances on the last day of each month."
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Amazon EC2 option is best for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns?",
    "options": [
      "Spot Instances",
      "On-Demand Instances",
      "Reserved Instances",
      "Dedicated Hosts"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following must be specified when launching a new Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Windows instance? (Choose two)",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Machine Image (AMI)",
      "Amazon EC2 instance type",
      "Password for the administrator account",
      "The Amazon EC2 instance ID"
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      2,
      3
    ]
  }
]